{
    "warmup": [
        {
            "id": "w-1-0",
            "question": "yellow impolite",
            "options": [
                "yellowIndolent",
                "yellowImpolite",
                "youngInternet",
                "yellowImpact"
            ],
            "format": "camelCase",
            "answer": "yellowImpolite"
        },
        {
            "id": "w-0-0",
            "question": "conflict earth",
            "options": [
                "conflict-earth",
                "conflict-essay",
                "concrete-event",
                "conflict-each"
            ],
            "format": "kebab-case",
            "answer": "conflict-earth"
        },
        {
            "id": "w-4-0",
            "question": "frequent reaction",
            "options": [
                "frequentReaction",
                "feedbackResource",
                "frequentRelative",
                "frequentResearch"
            ],
            "format": "camelCase",
            "answer": "frequentReaction"
        },
        {
            "id": "w-3-0",
            "question": "most wind",
            "options": [
                "month-window",
                "most-week",
                "most-wife",
                "most-wind"
            ],
            "format": "kebab-case",
            "answer": "most-wind"
        },
        {
            "id": "w-2-0",
            "question": "complete detailed",
            "options": [
                "comfort disaster",
                "complete detailed",
                "complete designer",
                "complete deserted"
            ],
            "format": "space",
            "answer": "complete detailed"
        },
        {
            "id": "w-5-0",
            "question": "innocent flowery",
            "options": [
                "interestFluffy",
                "innocentFeature",
                "innocentFlashy",
                "innocentFlowery"
            ],
            "format": "camelCase",
            "answer": "innocentFlowery"
        }
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "1-2",
            "question": "chain part",
            "options": [
                "chain puny",
                "chain pink",
                "chain part",
                "chest pace"
            ],
            "format": "space",
            "answer": "chain part"
        },
        {
            "id": "1-0",
            "question": "chain part",
            "options": [
                "chain-pink",
                "change-pack",
                "chain-part",
                "chain-pace"
            ],
            "format": "kebab-case",
            "answer": "chain-part"
        },
        {
            "id": "4-0",
            "question": "tight plan",
            "options": [
                "title-puny",
                "tight-past",
                "tight-play",
                "tight-plan"
            ],
            "format": "kebab-case",
            "answer": "tight-plan"
        },
        {
            "id": "4-1",
            "question": "tight plan",
            "options": [
                "titlePace",
                "tightPast",
                "tightPink",
                "tightPlan"
            ],
            "format": "camelCase",
            "answer": "tightPlan"
        },
        {
            "id": "0-0",
            "question": "plain motor",
            "options": [
                "plain-motor",
                "plain-mode",
                "prior-moral",
                "plain-mobile"
            ],
            "format": "kebab-case",
            "answer": "plain-motor"
        },
        {
            "id": "1-1",
            "question": "chain part",
            "options": [
                "chainPale",
                "cheapPair",
                "chainPart",
                "chainPast"
            ],
            "format": "camelCase",
            "answer": "chainPart"
        },
        {
            "id": "4-2",
            "question": "tight plan",
            "options": [
                "tight play",
                "tight past",
                "tower pure",
                "tight plan"
            ],
            "format": "space",
            "answer": "tight plan"
        },
        {
            "id": "2-1",
            "question": "estate parent",
            "options": [
                "essayPaper",
                "estateParent",
                "estatePaltry",
                "estatePlayer"
            ],
            "format": "camelCase",
            "answer": "estateParent"
        },
        {
            "id": "2-2",
            "question": "estate parent",
            "options": [
                "expert partial",
                "estate parent",
                "estate poised",
                "estate polite"
            ],
            "format": "space",
            "answer": "estate parent"
        },
        {
            "id": "3-0",
            "question": "fast town",
            "options": [
                "fact-tame",
                "fast-total",
                "fast-torn",
                "fast-town"
            ],
            "format": "kebab-case",
            "answer": "fast-town"
        },
        {
            "id": "0-1",
            "question": "plain motor",
            "options": [
                "plainMotor",
                "plainMixed",
                "plainMoist",
                "priorMouse"
            ],
            "format": "camelCase",
            "answer": "plainMotor"
        },
        {
            "id": "0-2",
            "question": "plain motor",
            "options": [
                "plain motor",
                "plain mother",
                "plain moral",
                "play muted"
            ],
            "format": "space",
            "answer": "plain motor"
        },
        {
            "id": "2-0",
            "question": "estate parent",
            "options": [
                "estate-player",
                "estate-parent",
                "estate-party",
                "employ-parched"
            ],
            "format": "kebab-case",
            "answer": "estate-parent"
        },
        {
            "id": "3-1",
            "question": "fast town",
            "options": [
                "fastTotal",
                "fastTool",
                "firmTerm",
                "fastTown"
            ],
            "format": "camelCase",
            "answer": "fastTown"
        },
        {
            "id": "3-2",
            "question": "fast town",
            "options": [
                "free tour",
                "fast torn",
                "fast tool",
                "fast town"
            ],
            "format": "space",
            "answer": "fast town"
        }
    ]
}